//<========================WARNING======================================> 
//Questions and respective answers to be added in the same order in the array

var questions=[]

// var q1={
//     "id":1,
//     "Question":"Lorem ipsum",
//     "Option 1":"abhay",
//     "Option 2":"abahy",
//     "Option 3":"abhay",
//     "Option 4":"abhay"
// }


// var q2={
//     "id":2,
//     "Question":"Which is true about lambda oprators in Python?",
//     "Option 1":"They are used to declare anonymous functions in Python",
//     "Option 2":"They can take any number of arguments",
//     "Option 3":"They are restricted to a single expression - syntactically",
//     "Option 4":"All of the above"
// }


// var q3={
//     "id":3,
//     "Question":"Which is true about lambda oprators in Python?",
//     "Option 1":"They are used to declare anonymous functions in Python",
//     "Option 2":"They can take any number of arguments",
//     "Option 3":"They are restricted to a single expression - syntactically",
//     "Option 4":"All of the above"
// }
// var q4={
//     "id":4,
//     "Question":"Which is true about lambda oprators in Python?",
//     "Option 1":"They are used to declare anonymous functions in Python",
//     "Option 2":"They can take any number of arguments",
//     "Option 3":"They are restricted to a single expression - syntactically",
//     "Option 4":"All of the above"
// }
// var q5={
//     "id":5,
//     "Question":"Which is true about lambda oprators in Python?",
//     "Option 1":"They are used to declare anonymous functions in Python",
//     "Option 2":"They can take any number of arguments",
//     "Option 3":"They are restricted to a single expression - syntactically",
//     "Option 4":"All of the above"
// }
// var q6={
//     "id":6,
//     "Question":"Which is true about lambda oprators in Python?",
//     "Option 1":"They are used to declare anonymous functions in Python",
//     "Option 2":"They can take any number of arguments",
//     "Option 3":"They are restricted to a single expression - syntactically",
//     "Option 4":"All of the above"
// }
// var q7={
//     "id":7,
//     "Question":"Which is true about lambda oprators in Python?",
//     "Option 1":"They are used to declare anonymous functions in Python",
//     "Option 2":"They can take any number of arguments",
//     "Option 3":"They are restricted to a single expression - syntactically",
//     "Option 4":"All of the above"
// }
// var q8={
//     "id":8,
//     "Question":"Which is true about lambda oprators in Python?",
//     "Option 1":"They are used to declare anonymous functions in Python",
//     "Option 2":"They can take any number of arguments",
//     "Option 3":"They are restricted to a single expression - syntactically",
//     "Option 4":"All of the above"
// }
// var q9={
//     "id":26,
//     "Question":"Which is true about lambda oprators in Python?",
//     "Option 1":"They are used to declare anonymous functions in Python",
//     "Option 2":"They can take any number of arguments",
//     "Option 3":"They are restricted to a single expression - syntactically",
//     "Option 4":"All of the above"
// }
// var q10={
//     "id":10,
//     "Question":"Which is true about lambda oprators in Python?",
//     "Option 1":"They are used to declare anonymous functions in Python",
//     "Option 2":"They can take any number of arguments",
//     "Option 3":"They are restricted to a single expression - syntactically",
//     "Option 4":"All of the above"
// }
// var q11={
//     "id":11,
//     "Question":"Which is true about lambda oprators in Python?",
//     "Option 1":"They are used to declare anonymous functions in Python",
//     "Option 2":"They can take any number of arguments",
//     "Option 3":"They are restricted to a single expression - syntactically",
//     "Option 4":"All of the above"
// }
// var q12={
//     "id":12,
//     "Question":"Which is true about lambda oprators in Python?",
//     "Option 1":"They are used to declare anonymous functions in Python",
//     "Option 2":"They can take any number of arguments",
//     "Option 3":"They are restricted to a single expression - syntactically",
//     "Option 4":"All of the above"
// }
// var q13={
//     "id":13,
//     "Question":"Which is true about lambda oprators in Python?",
//     "Option 1":"They are used to declare anonymous functions in Python",
//     "Option 2":"They can take any number of arguments",
//     "Option 3":"They are restricted to a single expression - syntactically",
//     "Option 4":"All of the above"
// }
// var q14={
//     "id":14,
//     "Question":"Which is true about lambda oprators in Python?",
//     "Option 1":"They are used to declare anonymous functions in Python",
//     "Option 2":"They can take any number of arguments",
//     "Option 3":"They are restricted to a single expression - syntactically",
//     "Option 4":"All of the above"
// }
// var q15={
//     "id":15,
//     "Question":"Which is true about lambda oprators in Python?",
//     "Option 1":"They are used to declare anonymous functions in Python",
//     "Option 2":"They can take any number of arguments",
//     "Option 3":"They are restricted to a single expression - syntactically",
//     "Option 4":"All of the above"
// }

var q1={
    "id":1,
    "Question":"What is the output of print 'Hello World'[::-1]",
    "Option 1":"dlroW olleH",
    "Option 2":"world Hello",
    "Option 3":"d",
    "Option 4":"None of the above"
}
 
data1={
    id:1,
    "answer":1
}
 
 
var q2={
    "id":2,
    "Question":"How many standard data types are there in Python",
    "Option 1":"5",
    "Option 2":"4",
    "Option 3":"3",
    "Option 4":"6"
}
 
data2={
    id:2,
    "answer":1
}
 
var q3={
    "id":3,
    "Question":"Which of these is a vector function in c++  vector<int> v",
    "Option 1":"v.begin()",
    "Option 2":"v.resize()",
    "Option 3":"v.reserve()",
    "Option 4":"All of the above"
}
 
data3={
    id:3,
    "answer":4
}


 
 
var q4={
    "id":4,
    "Question":"Which type of copy is shown in the code below? l1=[[10, 20], [30, 40], [50, 60]] ls=list(l1) ls [[10, 20], [30, 40], [50, 60]]",
    "Option 1":"Shallow copy",
    "Option 2":"Deep copy",
    "Option 3":"Memberwise",
    "Option 4":"All of the above"
}
data4={
    id:4,
    "answer":1
}
 
var q5={
    "id":5,
    "Question":"Which of the statements regarding dictionaries is false?",
    "Option 1":"The values of the dictionary can be accessed as dict[key]",
    "Option 2":"Values of a dictionary must be unique",
    "Option 3":"Values of a dictionary can be a mixture of letters and numbers",
    "Option 4":"More than one key can have the same value"
}
data5={
    id:5,
    "answer":2
}
var q6={
    "id":6,
    "Question":"Which of the following is not immutable?",
    "Option 1":"str",
    "Option 2":"list",
    "Option 3":"set",
    "Option 4":"frozenset"
}
data6={
    id:6,
    "answer":2
}
 

 
var q7={
    "id":7,
    "Question":"Predict the output in python shell 12^7.",
  "Option 1":"35831808",
  "Option 2":"11",
  "Option 3":"13",
  "Option 4":"Error"
}
data7={
    id:7,
    "answer":2
}
var q8={
    "id":8,
    "Question":"Which of the following data types doesn't allow duplicate values?",
    "Option 1":"tuples",
    "Option 2":"list",
    "Option 3":"set",
    "Option 4":"dictionary"
}
data8={
    id:8,
     "answer":3
}
var q9={
    "id":9,
    "Question":"In computer world,Trojan refers to",
    "Option 1":"virus",
    "Option 2":"malware",
    "Option 3":"worm",
    "Option 4":"spyware"
}
data9={
    id:9,
     "answer":2
}

var q10={
    "id":10,
    "Question":"How do you find the 3rd element from last in a single pass?",
    "Option 1":"Use one pointer, start with the start and traverse the whole array, reaching the last",
    "Option 2":"Use two pointers, with one at the start and the other at the end. Increasing one pointer and decreasing the other one by one 3 times gives the result at the second pointer.",
    "Option 3":"Traverse through the array from first to last and then go back three times",
    "Option 4":"Start from the last of the array and take three steps forward to reach third from the start."
}
 
data10={
    id:10,
    "answer":2
}
 

var q11={
    "id":11,
    "Question":"Given two arrays 1,2,3,4,5 and 2,3,4,5,6 find which number is not present in the second array",
    "Option 1":"Put elements of the second array in Hashtable and for every element of the first array, check if present in hash or not.",
    "Option 2":"Create a new array consisting of both the arrays and check if first half equal to second half.",
    "Option 3":"The numbers in both the arrays needs to be different always to find if present in the second array",
    "Option 4":"The array elements canâ€™t be checked with each other for each element in first array is unique."
}
 
data11={
    id:11,
    "answer":1
}
 

 

 

var q12={
    "id":12,
    "Question":"What Is Rstrip() In Python?",
    "Option 1":"Duplicates the string but leaves out the whitespace characters from the end.",
    "Option 2":"Duplicates the string but removes all the whitespaces from a string.",
    "Option 3":"Copies the entire string into another variable.",
    "Option 4":"It is not a function in python."
}
 
data12={
    id:12,
    "answer":1
}
 
var q13={
    "id":13,
    "Question":"What Is a Dictionary In Python?",
    "Option 1":"A data structure in Python that is a mutable, or changeable, and has ordered sequence of elements.",
    "Option 2":"Used to look through all built-in functions and keywords in Python.",
    "Option 3":"A group of objects mapped to another group of objects.",
    "Option 4":"It is a sequence of immutable Python objects."
}
 
data13={
    id:13,
    "answer":3
}
 
var q14={
    "id":3,
    "Question":"What Is The Output of 10>>1",
    "Option 1":"Syntax Error.",
    "Option 2":"1",
    "Option 3":"10",
    "Option 4":"5"
}
 
data14={
    id:14,
    "answer":4
}
 
var q15={
    "id":15,
    "Question":"Which Of The Following Is Mutable In Python?",
    "Option 1":"List.",
    "Option 2":"Tuple.",
    "Option 3":"Both.",
    "Option 4":"None."
}
 
data15={
    id:15,
    "answer":1
}

var q16={
    "id":16,
    "Question":"How to find the two maximum numbers in a randomly arranged array of numbers?",
    "Option 1":"Take max() of array.",
    "Option 2":"Arrange the array in ascending order and take the first two elements in the array.",
    "Option 3":"Take the array and find the last two elements.",
    "Option 4":"Take two loops and arrange in descending order. Take first two elements in the new array"
}
 
data16={
    id:16,
    "answer":4
}

var q17={
	"id":17,
	"Question":"Which data type is used to hold a key value store",
	"Option 1":"Array",
	"Option 2":"Linked list",
	"Option 3":"stack",
	"Option 4":"Dictionary"
}
data17={
	id:17,
	"answer":4
}

var q18={
    "id":18,
    "Question":"Which of these is not true for Python?",
    "Option 1":"It supports automatic garbage collection",
    "Option 2":"It can be easily integrated with C, C++, COM, ActiveX, CORBA, and Java",
    "Option 3":"It provides very high-level dynamic data types and supports dynamic type checking",
    "Option 4":"It is strictly Object Oriented"
}
data18={
    id:18,
    "answer":4
}
 

 

var q19={
    "id":19,
    "Question":"Which Of The Following is the first search engine ?",
    "Option 1":"Google",
    "Option 2":"Archie",
    "Option 3":"AltaVista",
    "Option 4":"WAIS"
}
data19={
    id:19,
    "answer":2
}

var q20={
    "id":20,
    "Question":"What is the output of 13 << 2?",
    "Option 1":"3",
    "Option 2":"52",
    "Option 3":"26",
    "Option 4":"6"
}
data20={
    id:20,
    "answer":2
}

 

 

var q21={
    "id":21,
    "Question":"If a function does not return any value, what value is shown when executed in the shell?",
    "Option 1":"bool",
    "Option 2":"int",
    "Option 3":"None",
    "Option 4":"void"
}
data21={
    id:21,
    "answer":3
}
 



questions.push(q1)
questions.push(q2)
questions.push(q3)
questions.push(q4)
questions.push(q5)
questions.push(q6)
questions.push(q7)
questions.push(q8)
questions.push(q9)
questions.push(q10)
questions.push(q11)
questions.push(q12)
questions.push(q13)
questions.push(q14)
questions.push(q15)
questions.push(q16)
questions.push(q17)
questions.push(q18)
questions.push(q19)
questions.push(q20)
questions.push(q21)





module.exports=questions